Narrator: 1
A1: Can I help you?
B1: Yes, I’d like a latte, please.
A1: Regular or large?
B1: Large, please.
A1: For here or to go?
B1: For here.
A1: That’s $3.40, please.
B1: Here you are. $3.40.
Narrator: 2
A2: Where are my car keys?
I can’t find them anywhere.
B2: I don’t know.
In your jacket pocket?
A2: No, they aren’t there.
B2: How about on the hall table?
A2: No.
B2: Are you sure you don’t have them?
A2: Absolutely sure.
B2: Look in the living room.
Narrator: 3
A3: Oh no, it’s 20 minutes late.
B3: Is there a waiting room somewhere?
It’s really cold here on the platform.
A3: No, I don’t think so.
B3: What time is it now?
A3: Six fifteen.
We can take the six twenty, but it’s a slow train.
B3: No, let’s wait, then.
Narrator: 4
A4: OK, come on, everyone, out here.
Stand together under the tree.
OK! Are you ready?
Carole, I can’t see you.
Can you stand next to Jim?
OK, ready? Say cheese!
Narrator: 5
A5: … So, Mr. Bartlett. Do you have any questions you’d like to ask?
B5: Uh, yes. On the website it says the hours are from 10 to 6.
What about the weekends?
A5: The hours are 10 to 6 on the weekends too, but you get paid overtime on Sundays.
Saturday counts as a normal day.
But if you work on a Saturday, you have a weekday free.
The contract clearly says five days a week, with possibilities of overtime.
B5: Oh, right.